♪ La la la la la la la ♪
Hi, Patrick!
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
嗨，帕特里克！
I just had another great--
wait a minute.
我刚刚又经历了一次伟大的——
等一下。
Hey, what's wrong?
嘿，怎么了？
I think I'm growing a nose.
我觉得我的鼻子要长了
I don't want a nose!
我不要鼻子！
Patrick, wait!
帕特里克，等等！
Hey, look, Patrick.
You just lost a tooth.
嘿，看，帕特里克。
你刚刚失去了一颗牙齿。
And if you put that tooth
under your pillow tonight,
如果你把那颗牙齿
今晚你的枕头底下，
the Tooth Fairy with come
and take the tooth
牙仙子来了
并取出牙齿
and leave you a quarter.
并留给你四分之一。
A quarter for just one tooth?
四分之一只换一颗牙齿？
Jackpot!
大奖！
Good night, teethies.
晚安，牙牙们。
Who says a life
of crime doesn't pay?
谁说一生
犯罪没有报酬？
Huh?
啊？
Sleep punch!
睡觉打拳！
Whoa! Ow!
哇！噢！
Who goes there?
谁去那里？
The Tooth Fairy!
牙仙子！
I gotta show SpongeBob!
我要给海绵宝宝看！
Hey, come on!
嘿，来吧！
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
You were right!
你是对的！
The Tooth Fairy came,
and I got him!
牙仙子来了，
我抓住了他！
Ahh!
啊！
Ooh!
哦！
I didn't do it!
我没有做！
Patrick, you-you-you really
did catch the Tooth Fairy!
帕特里克，你-你-你真的
确实抓住了牙仙子！
I told ya!
我告诉你了！
Wow.
哇。
He didn't give me a quarter,
but look.
他没有给我五分钱，
但你看。
I found these precious jewels
in his bag.
我找到了这些珍贵的珠宝
在他的包里。
What are you chowderheads
yapping about?
你们是什么杂烩
喋喋不休？
Tooth Fairy?
- Don't worry.
牙仙子？
- 不用担心。
You don't have
to play dumb with us.
你没有
和我们一起装傻。
Your secret is safe.
你的秘密是安全的。
Please let us ride along
with you tonight.
请让我们一起骑行
今晚和你在一起。
And be your Tooth Fairy assistants.
成为您的牙仙助手。
Yeah.
是的。
I'm the Tooth Fairy.
我是牙仙子
And I could use
a little help scoring loot--
我可以用
对获得战利品有一点帮助——
I mean, collecting teeth.
我的意思是，收集牙齿。
both: Yay!
两人：耶！
It's gonna be a long night.
这将是一个漫长的夜晚。
Ooh, hey!
哦，嘿！
I bet we could find
some teeth here.
我打赌我们能找到
这里有一些牙齿。
Pull over.
- Ahh!
套衫。
- 啊！
Now, this guy drinks
a lot of soda,
现在，这家伙喝酒了
很多苏打水，
so I'm sure he's got
a few loose teeth for us.
所以我确信他有
给我们一些松动的牙齿。
Let's get him.
我们来抓住他吧。
Here, use these special
Tooth Fairy masks.
在这里，使用这些特殊的
牙仙面具。
Ha-ha-ha!
哈哈哈！
Amateurs.
业余爱好者。
- Hey, look, it's Bubble--
- Can it!
- 嘿，看，这是泡泡--
- 可以吗！
Now, why don't you mugs shake
down Tiny here for some teeth?
现在，你的杯子为什么不摇动
小小在这里找牙齿吗？
I'm gonna look for teeth
in those valuables over there.
我要找牙齿
在那儿的那些贵重物品里。
Huh?
啊？
Only the Tooth Fairy gets
to laugh like that.
只有牙仙子才能得到
像那样笑。
Shh.
嘘。
I don't feel any teeth, Patrick.
我感觉不到任何牙齿，帕特里克。
Well, I feel a bunch of them.
嗯，我感觉有很多。
Ooh.
哦。
This one's really loose.
这个实在是太松了
I'm sure the Tooth Fairy won't
mind if we help it out.
我确信牙仙子不会
介意我们帮忙解决吗。
Ah!
啊!
Barnacle Boy!
藤壶男孩！
Hmm.
唔。
Agh!
啊啊！
Ooh, is this where you keep
the pillow money?
哦，这就是你放的地方吗
枕头钱？
Wow, teeth are sure worth a lot
these days.
哇，牙齿确实很值钱
这些天。
Come on, let's get
more teeth.
来吧，我们来吧
更多牙齿。
You've got the best job ever.
你已经得到了有史以来最好的工作。
Whoa--oof!
哇——噢！
both: Ooh.
两人：哦。
both: Whoa!
两人：哇！
Whoa!
哇！
Oh, oh!
哦，哦！
Mm.
毫米。
Whoa.
哇哦。
Right, ah, oh.
对啊，哦。
Ahh!
啊！
You stooges really gave
the Tooth Fairy
你们这些傀儡真的付出了
牙仙子
a lot of help tonight.
今晚有很多帮助。
Even if you also gave me
a headache.
就算你也给了我
头痛。
I like helping!
我喜欢帮忙！
Well, I think we got time
for one last job
好吧，我想我们还有时间
最后一份工作
if you're in.
如果你在的话。
Hey!
That's where Mr. Krabs lives.
嘿！
那是蟹老板住的地方。
He's my daytime boss.
You're my nighttime boss.
他是我白天的老板。
你是我的夜间老板。
Wait.
等待。
Watch out for booby traps.
小心陷阱。
I helped Mr. Krabs install the
security system myself, so--
我帮蟹老板安装了
我自己的安全系统，所以——
Here's one!
I'll disarm it!
这是一个！
我会解除它的武装！
- Patrick, no!
- Oops.
- 帕特里克，不！
- 哎呀。
Hello?
Who's down there?
你好？
谁在下面？
I'm calling the police.
我要报警。
Yes, police?
Come quick!
是的，警察？
快来吧！
I heard a noise.
我听到一声响动。
Oh, no, we woke him up!
Let's get out of here.
哦，不，我们把他吵醒了！
我们离开这里吧。
Ahh!
啊！
both: Shh!
两人：嘘！
Whaa...
哇...
ah, SpongeBob, Patrick.
啊，海绵宝宝，帕特里克。
What in the name of Poseidon's
pantaloons are you doing?
以波塞冬之名
你在做什么吗？
Why have you tripped
me burglar alarm?
为什么你绊倒了
我防盗报警器？
And why do you have
those burglar sacks?
为什么你有
那些防盗袋？
And why are you wearing
burglar masks?
你为什么穿着
防盗面具？
And why are you
with that burglar?
而你为什么是
和那个窃贼？
Wait a minute.
等一下。
Are you burglars?
你们是窃贼吗？
I'll take a burglar
with cheese.
我来抓贼
配奶酪。
We're not burglars.
我们不是窃贼。
We were just assisting
the Tooth Fairy here.
我们只是帮忙
牙仙子在这里。
Hello.
你好。
That ain't no Tooth Fairy.
I should know.
那不是牙仙子。
我应该知道。
I sold all my teeth to the real
Tooth Fairy years ago.
我把我所有的牙齿都卖给了真人
几年前的牙仙子。
Oh, no, the fuzz!
哦，不，是绒毛！
You gotta get me out of here!
你得带我离开这里！
I don't know.
我不知道。
Mr. Krabs says you're not
the real Tooth Fairy.
蟹老板说你不是
真正的牙仙子。
Huh?
Of course I am!
啊？
我当然是！
You just gotta believe!
你只需要相信！
That's all, yeah.
仅此而已，是的。
I believe in you,
Tooth Fairy!
我相信你，
牙仙子！
Goodbye, Mr. Krabs!
再见，蟹老板！
Those two are so gullible.
那两个人真是太容易受骗了。
Oh, look!
This rope says "pull me."
哦，看！
这根绳子说的是“拉我”。
Wah!
哇！
- Whoa!
- Ahh!
- 哇！
- 啊！
We can't go any farther!
我们不能再走得更远了！
The jig is up!
What are we gonna do?
吉吉起来了！
我们要做什么？
You're a Tooth Fairy!
You can fly!
你是牙仙子！
你可以飞！
Fly to safety!
飞向安全！
What?
both: Fly!
什么？
两人：飞吧！
Ahh!
啊！
Don't forget your teeth!
别忘了你的牙齿！
Or your boat!
或者你的船！
Ahh!
啊！
You know, Patrick,
I get the feeling
你知道，帕特里克，
我有感觉
that wasn't
the real Tooth Fairy.
那不是
真正的牙仙子。
Of course not!
当然不是！
But I am!
但我是！
The real Tooth Fairy?
真正的牙仙子？
You two did a wonderful job
collecting teeth all night.
你们两个做得很好
整夜收集牙齿。
Therefore, I'm going
to make you
因此，我要去
让你
honorary Tooth Fairy assistants.
名誉牙仙助理。
Abraca--
阿布拉卡——
- Dental.
- Ooh.
- 牙科。
- 哦。
both: Huh?
两人：啊？
Ah, come on!
啊，来吧！
A tooth!
一颗牙齿！
And a quarter.
还有四分之一。
Abraca-dental!
阿布拉卡牙科！